Adarsh Sharma

Project Manager

Contact

Address

Jabalpur, MP, 482009

Phone

845 283 4884

E-mail

adarshsharma883@gmail.co

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/Adrocks123

www

https://adarshsharma.info/

Skills

Project planning and development

Very Good

Systems Installation, Configuration, and Upgrading

Very Good

New product introductions strategies

Good

Microsoft Active Directory

Average

Programming Languages

Resourceful Project Manager with 3 years of expertise in organizing business operations, financial oversight and resource management to achieve smooth flow and project operations. Leads procurement of resources including equipment and supplies. Monitors projects by adhering to production schedule and budget, managing production team, identifying problems and providing targeted solutions. Knowledgeable in accounting principles, bookkeeping, budget and financial management.

Work History

2019-07 -Current

Senior Project Executive

SAARC CASES, COIMBATORE, Tamil Nadu

- Updated operational methods, oversaw accounting procedures, tracked information and compiled data to improve efficiency.
- Developed and initiated projects, managed costs, and monitored performance.
- Reined in project costs while meeting key milestones.
- Modified and directed project plans to meet organizational needs.
- Headed project teams specializing in design and launch activities.
- Provided accurate, detailed quantity take-offs from project drawings and technical specifications.
- Drove team success through shared vision and recognition of quality performance.
- Eliminated discrepancies in progress by reviewing performance, spend and timeline.
- Implement CI/CD Pipeline with Jenkins to get the process in automation.
- Manage web service like AWS for product streaming
- Hands onn experience in different project management tools including our tool Edifybiz

•

2017-12 -2019-07

Freelancer

freelancer.com, Jabalpur, Madhya Pradesh

- Worked on various technologies such as github, Ansible, Pagerduty etc.
- Design various solution using .Net Framework and

Good

Project Management

Very Good

VmWare VCenter Servers

Good

VmWare Virtualization

Good

Strategic planning

Good

Systems Design

Documentation

Very Good

Testing and Conversion Plans

Good

Software Development Lifecycle

Very Good

Procedure development

Good

Business process re-engineering

Very Good

Advanced problem solving

Good

Cross-functional communication

Very Good

Software

Github, .Net core MVC,

- different languages like html, css, js, c#, sql
- Implement various functions fo continuous
 Integration using jenkins like administrative part,
 create different jobs, build different pipelines,
 backup/RBAC etc.
- Implement various tools for bug racking like mantis,
 Wireframes and workflows like pencil, adobe XD,
 Mail design linke mailchimp etc.
- Volunteered for extra shifts during holidays and other busy periods to alleviate staffing shortages.
- Prioritized helping customers over completing other routine tasks in store.
- Used product knowledge, sales abilities and customer relations skills to drive substantial sales increases in scalability and bug free products.

Languages

C#, HTML, JS, CSS, SQL

Education

2013-07 -	Bachelor of Engineering: Information
2017-07	Technology
	Rajiv Gandhi Technical University - Bhopal
2012-03 -	High School Diploma
2013-03	Saraswati Shishu Mandir Ranjhi - Jabalpur

Accomplishments

- Resolved product issue through consumer testing.
- Achieved manual load decrement by introducing netcampus for performing automation tasks.
- Achieved customer satisfaction by completing ERP for education sector with accuracy and efficiency.

Jenkins, Remedy, Pagerduty, Mantis, Ansible. Apache products like tomcat, maven

Very Good